{
    "id": "f16926d6a7ed441b8791e1f8431731a8",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The burning rubber gave …………………. acrid smoke.",
            "description": "To give off is to emit. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "531ca09edbc44e029fd2ad71c60b071d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like the idea but I will ……………………… to it.",
            "description": "To acquiesce is to consent or agree.",
            "answers": [
                "acquiesce",
                "acquaint",
                "adopt"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7eba1d4a7c1f439ebc3a9343c7ad0701"
        },
        {
            "question": "The painting is the museum’s most recent …………………………",
            "description": "An acquisition is a material possession.",
            "answers": [
                "acquisition",
                "acquirement"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f518be8ae6574b0ab41eba6fe4037ade"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is an ……………………… person, always wanting things.",
            "description": "Acquisitive means greedy",
            "answers": [
                "inquisitive",
                "acquisitive",
                "impulsive"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a12dc19b66b64132b37a3e786dbddb9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The jury …………………….. the defendant of all charges.",
            "description": "To acquit is to declare innocent.",
            "answers": [
                "condoned",
                "acquitted",
                "suspected"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54b19c51e84c4e7586c92fe175d44f7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fire department was called into ……………………….. when the alarm sounded.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "act",
                "action"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "492134810f5d4e3f97421b6b25f69366"
        },
        {
            "question": "The chameleon ………………………. to its surroundings by changing color.",
            "description": "To adapt is to adjust. ",
            "answers": [
                "adapts",
                "adopts",
                "accords"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da32c93cf47e4b67b31de089352d5a8f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The TV series is an …………………………. of a novel.",
            "description": "Adaptation means a modified version.",
            "answers": [
                "adaptation",
                "adoption",
                "adoptation"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "955fb9c38e7640f7bd13aab146d199ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………………. at organizational work.",
            "description": "Adept means skilled.",
            "answers": [
                "adept",
                "adopt",
                "adapt"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5be20389639542439dec732e66f11247"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting was …………………………… until tomorrow at 11 am.",
            "description": "Adjourned means postponed",
            "answers": [
                "adjoined",
                "adjourned",
                "adjudicated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8653385861f6418198f8bff21d4d88ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ……………………….. for all children to have polio shots.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advisable",
                "advised",
                "advicable",
                "adviced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39cda769f6bd44ee8bf38769fabb01f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He and his brother are very much …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "alike"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cfcb4fb2a19f4227b517afe59638ca8c"
        }
    ]
}